Hello, thank you. Hello, hello, me. Hello, my close friend from the Cold War. Hello,
movies, movies, etc. Hello, River 4-gu, hello,
Min. Hello,
new person, Kim Nan-hee, and Annie. Hello.
[Music]
Hello, hello, Ision.
Nice to meet you. There
are no acorns. Um,
today, more
culture. I brought the coffee story bed.
On the street, the park and the TV loft. Ah, the
TV. This looks like a mosquito's face.
[Music] It
's 8:01 now, so I
'll start in about 10 minutes after opening. It
's been 4 or 2 minutes.
Oh, well, this is
something I've heard in the chatroom sometimes, but I've also heard it told a few times to other people.
When we meet offline, we
talk a lot in our chatroom. But if possible,
especially regarding questions, 2.7 3, I
can really understand everything in one word. If it's not a question that ends with "no, yes, no," I
hope you use the cafe Q&A board as much as possible.
That way, people who do things can leave some and look at them. The
chatroom is a little  Because the idea is so strong,
there are many people who don't have spin and aren't there, so I'll make a question board or a bulletin
board for that. I'll make it the first bulletin board. I'd like you to make it a broadcast topic. I'd
like you to
cover things in depth, so you can do them like this. If you call it a Yangyu Eu
form, I won't make that form, so I
don't think it's a bulletin board, so I
think it would be good to upload things like that.
Why is this not taking charge? It seemed like chicken curry wasn't uploading, but
today, the executive gritted his teeth and moved to 5 like this 3,
but this is also my head like this.
Ah, what is it? I don't know if you can change it on your own. It
will be maintained.
Hello, Mong-ttang, Pung-ran. Hello, Join, blind Chris 2,
especially Bin. Hello, it
's past.
Hello, K, Jenny. Eat,
um.
And just 4,
2, 5, Tao, corruption, terminology.
Ter, point, red, action, basis. But since I did it, I'll write some 38 accompaniments. The
genre world is don't eat. First of all, at least
three genres. You said not to eat, but Nanga Burner  Can't I eat number 1 too?
This is a
male script. Regardless of whether it's an
egg white or not, it's better to skip the egg white. No matter how good it is on its own, it's bad for the intestines.
B. It's the same in a combined environment, so
if you have a bad intestines, it's probably better to skip the egg whites.
The yolk is usually fine. There are many reasons why people are told
not to eat eggs, and when you have a bad intestines, it's mostly
because of the factors.
After getting a vaccine or
something, the egg whites are included as substances that trigger an immune response, such as JB Ahn Hyuk, a trigger, or something.
[Music]
The yolk is
big. If you cook it, it's okay. Even if it's
not a huge amount, it's still
absorbed to some extent. It's the vitamin D6 that's destroyed the most. In fact, the yolk doesn't have much P6,
but now, other things like P1 are also destroyed a lot. So,
if you can cook it, it's not bad to eat it.
But it's okay to cook it. How can I get rid of it?
The cause of tinnitus.
But these are
actually difficult to pinpoint right away. I don't know what kind of
eating habits the person wanted to have, what kind of lifestyle they have,
how they have lived so far, how old they are now, or
what other conditions they are in.
But basically, vaginitis is like that,
so before,
eat enough of the 3 Balance, and in fact, most problems here will
naturally disappear if you cut out sugar and seeds.
* I
think we need to look at what you are doing first.
Polysaccharides. Hello, Carpe Diem. Hello, Far Kane.
Hello, Hongsu Tong. If you
ask, "Is it because eggs are worse for the intestines than this product or pork?",
well, eggs are bad, dairy products are worse, pork is bad, and everything
seems bad. It's not like that naturally.
Eggs are made up of the whites and the heart. This product
can be used cold, and pork can be eaten in salted form. Why is that
bad for the intestines?
Hello, Can.
Let's start the 3 broadcast. I
think it's a more appropriate environment to see it like this.
Body type  Hello,
this is almost the last part, but it suddenly
became a spoiler.
Oh,
just a moment. Um,
I couldn't hear the card sound at the beginning, but there's nothing I
can do about it. 4 3 3 3 The scent is really believer. When you count the bees, suck it up in a thousand dimensions. Do the bees hit? No, I think I need to put my DC
in the toilet. Yes, for sure, rub it in the fish tank like this and use it with Bellis Pansy.
Ah, io. It's not good for your head.
But the design itself isn't always good.
As I told you, you should
never do a couple right now.
Ah, 5.
Through the movie, this setting is like an advertisement.
And then, in the middle of the broadcast, I've eaten 40
computers. It's a laptop that was used by Labo 3.
The
company has to go there from time to time to get certified, but it
hasn't been certified for a while, and it asks for certification.
That's when Microsoft's Windows 10
product certification was done. In other words, the screen changes to blue. I
'll start by telling you. Person, new belly fat notice. Hello,
today, I've prepared a story about coffee.
When talking about a healthy diet, one thing that can't be left out is  I think this is about coffee.
I haven't really talked about it in detail in the past, but I've
briefly
talked about how coffee isn't good for us and how we should drink it if we really want to.
Oh, and recently, I said that drinking coffee is like hammering the adrenal glands to release adrenaline.
Many people seemed shocked, so I brought it here to look into
why I don't drink coffee in more detail.
Before that, let's talk about the panel.
Anyway, Koreans really, really love coffee. There are so many
cafes. The
number of cafes is 100,000, and sales are also high, but a cup of coffee is almost 100%.
Even so, last year, Starbucks sales almost reached 100. It
doesn't make sense to me to do that. As a side note, if you
add up the market capitalization of the three major entertainment agencies in Korea, SM, JYP, and YG, that's how much they would be.
Starbucks' sales last year were in Korea, not around the world, but
in Korea.
Anyway, do we like coffee this much?
Of course, it's because drinking it like this makes you feel good, keeps you cool, and tastes good.
But how does coffee bring about these effects I mentioned earlier? Let's
learn about the mechanism of action of coffee. The first thing that is known about
how coffee acts on us and our bodies in the spring is that it
binds to adenosine receptors. What this means is that there are receptors for adenosine, a neurotransmitter
in our brain that
excites the nerves, like dopamine. If you
think about it in terms of receptors, adenosine 2
comes in and
makes our body feel drowsy and lethargic, which ultimately leads to sleep and
recovery. As it
leaves like this, we react and
become lethargic and fall asleep. It's
a bit strange to say caffeine, but it contains 2 caffeine.
Instead of adenosine receptors,
caffeine enters like this and
binds instead. It's like a jacket, right?
By binding instead, the adrenal machine works and
prevents us from feeling drowsy.
Coffee also stimulates the sympathetic nervous system.
Coffee affects the hypothalamus and the adrenal axis, and
significantly reduces the production of adrenaline and corticotropin-releasing hormone.
This means that our body enters a fight-or-flight state, and energy is
generated.
Logical thinking is clouded, but reaction speed increases, and these effects can be achieved.
Also, when the brush is stimulated like this, the sympathetic nervous system is working at 9 o'clock. The west
starts and Adele's ring, adrenocorticotropin-releasing hormone, is bursting out. These
hormones are called cyclic AMPs in our body.
Yes, cyclic AMPs are also called camps.
This AMP is a substance made from ATP, the cellular gasoline, the fuel of the cells, and it
makes each of our cells work hard.
But originally,  The production of AMP in the elderly is like this, like a certain amount of life and death, and
when it reaches this point, it should stop like this.
Additional production should be naturally suppressed. This company suppresses this
like this, but
there is adenosine.
But now, if you drink coffee, the caffeine will
stop the peak braking. By suppressing adenosine, the
AMP in your chain
can be produced indefinitely without the brakes being
applied. If we compare our body to a running car, it's like stepping on the accelerator and then
releasing the brake.
Coffee also has a central nervous system effect. All of these things
come together to
temporarily make us feel like Superman, without getting tired, with a
clear mind, and
even a good mood. Yes, that's the
mechanism of action of coffee. It's a difference in the order of magnitude.
It's a neurotransmitter produced by our adrenal glands, and it shakes up the production of stress hormones, and it
eliminates some of the brakes.
These actions are harmful, like cocaine, so they affect us.  It's exactly the same.
The process of how these drugs work in our generation is similar.
Sir, the drugs work in this way.
So, what are the side effects of coffee?
Of course, cocaine, heroin, and amphetamines
work in a similar mechanism, so the side effects are similar to our drugs, although to a different degree.
Let's look at the side effects of coffee. First, when
external stimulants like coffee continuously enter the body,
of course, the effect is good at first, and then,
as the saying goes, it's the same. At first, the effect is good, but as time goes on, the effect
decreases. It's
because the body always tries to maintain homeostasis. But why does the body adapt so quickly? It
tries to adapt. Coffee tricks the brain into feeling tired,
making it seem like it doesn't know how to be tired. It doesn't actually relieve fatigue.
That's why it
gradually increases
adenosine receptors to counteract mother. After Crank, the coffee I drink increases the number of adenosine receptors more than before,
so
now the adenosine receptors are like this, like this, and these two were all that needed to be filled,
but
this is caffeine, and it's sapo.  Here, as I fill it up, the receptors are getting more and
more blocked.
Hey, it's too much.
Like this, like this, like this. The picture is messed up.
As the adenosine receptors have increased, this has widened the coverage. To cover this,
to cover the coverage, it's
a bit strange to say, but a more
proliferative receptor is needed than before.
To enjoy the effects of the coffee you mentioned earlier, you need to drink more and more.
Why do coffee keep going down like this? It's not good to hit the ground running.
Let's talk about it later.
The problem is that if you don't drink coffee for even one day, that is, normally, you need receptors to taste up to here, but if you
keep drinking coffee, you'll have to pull down the aptitude for warding.
In this situation, think about not drinking coffee.
This is where you originally filled it. The caffeine is disappearing and it's like this. My son will come and
fill it.
In the meantime,
because of the many adenosine receptors, you will feel extremely tired as usual.
Also, as mentioned above, caffeine
stimulates the hypothalamus, which is the body's adrenal cortex.  It secretes stimulating hormones, and
these hormones stimulate the high cortisol corticosteroids, such as
dopamine, norepinephrine, and
catecholamines. Cortisol is a hormone that
should come and go periodically according to the circadian rhythm.
This is a morning, and the
text is a bit like that now,
but if I'm here in the morning, it's not like that. If I do this, it's a bit
bad. Local
self again. Ah, 3 in
the morning and
evening. If I'm here, when I draw a graph like this, here, I
understand. Cortisol
10 hours. Then, the original coat sound
drops like this from morning to evening, and then rises like this again the next morning.
This is our coating. In the morning, Czech Republic Te document peaks, and our
body is energized, opens its eyes, and
to give us the energy to live the day, we come out at this time, and
in the evening, it comes back like this. We need to organize everything that happened that day and
recover.
At this time, it hits the lowest point again.
This ups and downs should continue, but in a cafe.  If you continue to consume caffeine,
this stem gets damaged, and the cortisol response in the morning at Artimam
decreases. At this time, caffeine is consumed, and the coat line
turns here, then rises here, then rises here more, and this
cycle repeats,
breaking the natural cycle. When the
UV cycle is broken, the circadian rhythm is broken again. If
the rhythm is broken early,
people who don't drink coffee at all are fine even if they just sit still. However, people who are addicted to coffee or whose circadian rhythm is broken,
people whose cortisol cycle is broken due to caffeine need to drink more coffee every day to
function much more normally.
This situation is 20. This experiment
wasn't an experiment targeting snakes early in the day. The group that consumed melon caffeine
didn't have an increase in cortisol even when they drank coffee in the morning. In fact, it
was an experiment that showed that the coat habit just started to bounce back in the afternoon. It's an experiment that shows that it's
just a cafe, so it's not like you can make a gentleman.
And as a side effect that inevitably leads to the rhythm early, there are sleep problems.
Coffee affects the lifespan.  It may
seem obvious, but
this study even
said that the idea that coffee raises body temperature may actually just be covering up the lethargy caused by lack of sleep.
So, the habit of drinking coffee thinking that you need to drink coffee to feel energized is actually
driving away the lack of sleep and lethargy caused by coffee. It's a
human story.
Ah,
9. The
theory is that
coffee increases adenosine receptors and the
circadian rhythm is bad for sleep quality. If you look closely, you become more and more dependent on it and you have to
drink a lot. Like a normal person who doesn't drink a lot, that basic foundation becomes a state of drinking coffee.
Yes, if you want to live like a normal person who doesn't drink it, you have to drink coffee. But
then your body has changed.
But before we talk more about the effects of coffee, let's take a moment to
consider whether coffee is so bad that it deserves such criticism or whether it has that much caffeine.
Coffee really does have a lot more caffeine than you think.
Let's look at the caffeine content of representative caffeinated drinks.
First, everyone knows that cola has a certain amount of caffeine, right?
1 can  Next, without anything else, there's a bit more, and with Cobaco, a bit less, but this
house has about 30mg.
Hot Six Round Red Bull is a representative energy drink, right? One can of
Hot Six Red Bull contains about 60mg of caffeine in a 60g tablet.
And many people buy a tall Starbucks Americano that tastes like
250mg of caffeine.
If you add Satan on top of that, it'll be 225mg for an extra 600 won.
Now, if we look at the caffeine content of commercially available caffeine drinks in order of highest caffeine, it's like
this. I'm not sure if you're seeing this right now, but this long list is organized by high hand, and it's
all coffee. As for
energy drinks, how was the MBC? It's still a bit dark. It's a bit further down, and
we have to crack the sugar content to find the energy drink.
The problem doesn't end here.
Caffeine has a half-life of about 6 hours.
Now, if you drink this 00 hours and it
hits 6 hours, it's half, and after going through immigration, it's reduced to half again.
If you drink a Starbucks Americano at 12 o'clock, when it's
time, if you drink a Starbucks Americano at this time, you still have
25% more caffeine in your body than if you had a Six or Red Bull together at 6 o'clock in the evening.
75 mg.
But if you
drink a Starbucks Americano at 18 o'clock and 16:00, right? If several macho men drink one cup each at 2 o'clock, by 8 o'clock, they usually do, they'll have
110 2.5 mg. That
means they'll definitely have as much caffeine left as if they had a Six and two cans of Red Bull.
If you drink an Americano at 12 o'clock, if you drink just one,
by the time it's midnight, this kid will have 56 mg. That
means they'll have the same amount of caffeine left as if they had drank a can of Red Bull right at this time. If you
drink caffeine like this every day, the
continuous dopamine stimulation can reduce the dopamine receptors in the brain.
Adrenaline, orenoic acid, adrenaline, and catecholamines are also the
stimulation of the sympathetic nervous system. They cause
acute stress situations when we are fighting or worsening when we are in danger, such as when we are hunting or when we are in a bear trap or chasing a tiger, or when we are in a battle or war, or when we are in a great danger.
Without this urgent stress,
yes, but now that we are drinking coffee like this every day, our
bodies are changing into those that cannot live without this urgent stress.
It is like a drug addiction, we have become a body that cannot live without coffee.
Oh, and just in case, there is a lot of talk about it in the chatroom,
but I am saying this in case
anyone thinks that all these problems can be solved with just one word: decaffeinated coffee.
Caffeine is caffeine, but
coffee stimulates the sympathetic nervous system, raises blood pressure,
and causes other problems. It is not easy to get rid of caffeine.
There are many problems other than caffeine. Coffee itself is
basically the seeds of the coffee cherry, and
that is just it.  It
's not just about grinding it all up.
Coffee is basically made from the seeds of coffee cherries. We
grind the seeds of coffee cherries a lot, and you
have to remember that the ground powder is steeped in water. As
I mentioned, the original purpose of the seeds is to survive the dangers they face, and
plants don't keep only the good things in them because predators eat them. Of course, we
need to keep the seeds alive. In addition, there are problems with decaffeinated coffee beans themselves. They are
often contaminated with mold, and the quality is generally poor. Of course, this
could be solved if you could find and eat the highest quality teacafe coffee beans, but I'm not
sure if that's actually possible.
Anyway, continuing with the side effects of coffee,
coffee also improves nutrient absorption.
Vitamin B,
thiamine, and iron absorption are all important. As I mentioned in the story about being deceived last time, it
acts as a diuretic, so it removes salt, magnesium, calcium, and other nutrients.
Oh, and lastly, coffee isn't good for sleep.
First of all, coffee stimulates gastric acid secretion.
This is because coffee stimulates the secretion of stomach acid even on an empty stomach. What
he means is that if you consistently drink coffee on an empty stomach in the morning, you
waste your stomach glands when there is no food, and
when you actually eat, your stomach acid is not secreted well, so even if the phase is insufficient, you
can block it.
In addition, if you add that coffee can damage the stomach mucosa,
this study shows that the stomach mucosa is damaged after
drinking coffee. It is natural that you feel heartburn when drinking coffee on an empty stomach.
A lot of stomach acid is produced in the stomach, and the outlook is completely damaged.
But if coffee stimulates the secretion of stomach acid, wouldn't it be good to eat it with food like this? I
think that's why you might think that. But
let me tell you that's not necessarily true.
The caffeine in coffee relaxes the esophageal sphincter.
Accountant Matt Xantini. Those who own dogs or cats have probably heard of this. I
think everyone who has one knows that you shouldn't feed coffee or chocolate to pets like cats.
This means that the animals burn bromine, which is also called phosphorus.  Now, that's because
we're much more sensitive than the multiple substances in chocolate, but it
's also because of the 4th team of Tech. The 2nd Tech is a stimulant and a
tranquilizer at the same time. It's
very toxic to animals, especially those just starting out. When
it enters our bodies, it
acts like a stimulant,
stimulating the sympathetic nervous system and further stimulating the central nervous system. But at the
same time, it
acts as a tranquilizer by activating the sphincter muscles in our stomach and esophagus.
In other words, stingy coffee makes it easier for stomach acid and food to
reflux into the esophagus and pass undigested food into the small intestine.
10 each. Here's the stomach, here's the esophagus, and
here's the small intestine.
If reflux occurs, of course, the side will hurt, it will be bitter, and it will be stuffy. The
transplant cells will change, and problems may occur. If
undigested food passes through here, the
absorption amount will also be a problem. In the intestines.  Here's a chunk of meat that hasn't been broken down yet,
some sort of fruit chunks made for one serving, and
sugar, books, and words, and
it's like this. Think about it. In a cow's state, the food has all rotted and
become bitter, making it very easy for bacteria and fungi to proliferate in the small intestine.
And lastly, coffee itself can also trigger an immune response in the tissues of the intestines.
So, if you
listen to g, there's support now.
So, are you saying that we shouldn't drink walking? Are you saying that we should
break up now? Are you saying that there will be no coffee for the rest of our lives?
Many of you are probably experiencing honorifics or have already finished the video.
But this isn't necessarily true.
Judai Ola. Now, coffee, as I've mentioned so far,
has all these side effects. At the same time, as you've probably
all heard at least once,
there are studies that show that coffee has various positive effects. Drinking coffee regularly and things like that.
Those studies usually say that there are bad things here and good things there.
There are bad things, but there are also good things.
Or, in a similar setting, they get completely opposite results from other studies.
There are a lot of confusing parts, and it's
also a study on people who drank coffee slowly, so
there are a lot of ambiguous aspects.
Anyway, I'm not saying that coffee is unconditionally bad.
One thing that's certain is that there are some positive aspects, but the
negative aspects clearly have pros and cons, and it's
not worth drinking it every day despite the bad things.
In addition, it's like drinking coffee as a finishing touch, and the focus and performance that improves are like
drinking coffee, and the brain seems to get better, the body feels more energetic, and
these things just cover up the lack of sleep. It's
just because of the coffee withdrawal symptoms right before drinking the coffee, and
there's also an argument that it's not really the 2.2 that coffee purely brings. I'm
not saying that this is certain. It's like when
we do cocaine, we feel a surge of energy, our mind gets
really good, and our concentration skyrockets, but the
withdrawal symptoms are severe until the next cocaine dose, so the improvement when we definitely drink it next time is
just an improvement of the withdrawal symptoms.  It's the same.
So, I hope you don't become dependent on coffee anymore. I'm
not saying you should stop drinking coffee. I'm not saying you should stop drinking coffee.
People who are healthy and have good desk habits
like Amnam-dong in the morning are refreshing. It's not too much, but I do
n't think it's bad to have a cup of
coffee that is roasted, fragrant, of good quality, and brewed with 6-in-1 beans. I don't think it's bad. Besides, good coffee tastes really good. I also like coffee, so I
wanted to drink a lot of different types of coffee. So, I recommend that you
savor and enjoy coffee. I hope you do it rather than recommend it. I feel anxious without coffee, I can't live without coffee, and I have to drink
coffee to live a quiet life like others. I
'm just watching helplessly as I drink coffee, and
coffee is a
dominant food. It tastes good and is a food of choice. Caffeine is just a
secondary product that comes with the various flavors and tastes. If you think about it and drink it, I
hope you enjoy it by adding only the flavor.  These days, if a safe cup of coffee in the morning is just a
means to wake you up, rather than a way to do this, I'd cut down or quit for a while. I've
talked about this a lot before, but
since coffee works in a similar way to drugs, if you're addicted and dependent on coffee,
quitting is really not easy. The side effects can be severe, just like quitting drugs.
Quitting all at once can be incredibly difficult, so
I'm going to gradually reduce my coffee intake by one cup per day, or
cut it down to half of your usual intake, and when it reaches one cup, I'll stop drinking it completely. I'll try to cut it down as long as possible for
at least a week.
After that, I'll gradually reduce it again.
And if I could give you some rough guidelines on when to drink coffee, I do
n't think it's good to drink it right after waking up. I'd drink it about
two hours after waking up,
but in the morning, for example, let's say I wake up at 7 a.m., around
10 a.m. or before 9:30 a.m. As I
said before, I drink really good quality coffee.  I hope you choose good quality ones that are well-
roasted and freshly
roasted, and
then enjoy them. After that, I hope you don't drink
coffee. And it's hard to endure the feeling of emptiness after a while of not drinking coffee.
This is also a habit, so it can happen. In times like this, you
can look for other drinks. A
warm hump tea without caffeine is also good. You can
also drink warm lemon or lime juice.
Rooibos, chamomile, peppermint, and all these herbal teas are refreshing and
make you feel better.
I hope this video has given you enough reason to cut down on or quit coffee, at least for a while. 1. Those who are addicted to coffee and cut down or quit
often say that it's difficult at first, but after quitting, everything got better. So,
if there are people who are currently addicted, I hope you take a break. If the
video was helpful, please subscribe, like, comment, and set an alarm.
Yes, there are a lot of diet stories and cafes, so Kai Fashion would be nice.
Thank you for watching the long video. I'll end it like this today.
Okay, um, because
I did it with the sun, Mark.
Yes.  Should I see this? I wrote something for you. If you
came in the evening, you absolutely shouldn't drink coffee. After
lunch, you had a two-shot, and after dinner, you drank a caption. Um,
but this is the real story. It's the same. If you
drink 5 liters of HT on an empty stomach in the morning, it seems like it's really bad for your health.
oh, oh, this is too much. uh, what's the
limit? uh, uh,
is it covered? uh, uh, uh,
5.
Coffee should be enjoyed for its taste. It's
really filling. It's hard to
quit coffee when
you're full, but it
's more addictive than bread. It's like
that because it strongly secretes neurotransmitters. uh, [music] The side effects of coffee are not the same. As I mentioned earlier, coffee seeds stimulate the sympathetic nervous system,
raise blood pressure, and ca
n't be compared to energy drinks. I can't even hit it.
s Starbucks Americano tool 150mg. I
don't have it when I eat Biwon and drink coffee.
Tea is the same.
Seo Young-hee, I don't have any children, but I feel it a lot.
Bond is cheap,
but it's no different. No. Coffee comes out. Try it. Iron is the same.
5. If you
do it with less than caffeine tax,
you know, Kai padding, that
r,
that three teas
are included in the large parlor Messina guideline tea.
After you fully recover, you can do it.
Yes, add it. Of course, don't forget organic. It's a
problem with caffeine, but it's not necessarily just the caffeine molecule. The coffee itself is the problem.
Okay, so now you can do it, but you have to
think about the nuance carefully.
Cashier coffee is worse because of the sugar.
If you only consider the caffeine, espresso is better, but yes,
cold brew has the most caffeine because it brews the fastest.
I
've heard a lot of people say that they don't want to keep sipping that coffee all day long, right? To
some extent, it
doesn't seem like it's going to taste like that.
Yes, there's too much, so I'll go down and see since it doesn't seem to work. It's
cheap, but
Starbucks is really bad. Among them, they
roast their beans in the US and bring in beta, right?
This is roasting.  When roasting, the raw beans that were contaminated with mold are
destroyed by the high heat, including mycotoxins.
However, when roasted like Starbucks, they are contaminated during the roasting process, so there are many
people who say that drinking Starbucks' "Coffee of the Day" makes them sick. I
suspect that "Coffee of the Day" is not just about the coffee that doesn't last long and is sold cheaply. I do
n't know about M1, but
Starbucks's coffee doesn't taste good either.
If you're going to make a reservation, would
n't it be better to drink the best, at least the most delicious one that tastes good in your mouth, since it's not good for your body? It's not that
bad because the
Wonder beans from overseas don't exist, but when Wonder beans come in, they come alive and live, so
it's okay if they roast in Korea, but
when they bring in the beans, it's worse. The defeat is severe, and there's mold infection in the city center, and there's really no reason to go to Starbucks. If you're going to use that space, then it's fine, but it's cold, so go now.  Reading is really good, right? No one cares and you can just
drink it at home.
You hear a lot about it being sent from the roaster, right?
Buying good beans directly from there and
drinking them at home is the best.
Going to a cafe and drinking coffee is possible because of the space, not because you go there to drink coffee. I also do it when I go to a cafe.
Well, that's the thing, but paying for the space at home for the atmosphere is
nice, but I don't go there to drink coffee anymore.
In fact, there aren't many places like Starbucks where you can pay 5,000 won and
sit there all day.
Except for those cafes.
Hello, Mr. Ye-oh.
Hello, Mr. Lee Chaeng. Hello, these days in me.
In my opinion, if you're going to drink coffee, then, as I've been
saying, if you want to enjoy it,
of course you shouldn't go to Starbucks. Instead,
brew the highest quality coffee yourself and enjoy it in the style you want.
Think of it the same way as saying.
Don't just pour soju and cordially say you're going to get
drunk. It's
a bit more delicious and a bit healthier, but it's a bit strange.
Among them, it's closed and
more delicious and such, that is, this is a
single illustrator. I don't know for sure, but it's
not that bad. I do
n't think he would have recommended it for nothing because he's a person who is stubborn in his own way.
When making other things like myrtle r cream, vanilla is
very nutty. Do
n't buy the ones that are roasted and brought in. There's
no reason to buy them. In fact, really,
ah,
this is the one that comes from the roasting, of course I won't drink more, and even if it's
cheap, if you
drink coffee considering the price, it's
always at home, so of course it'll all be right. Yes,
just roasted coffee, if possible, roast it domestically, and
put in the young, unroasted ones. There are companies that
send the roasted ones from the roasting on the same day when you order coffee,
so I
think extracts like that are okay. And you don't use a lot of them,
just like Eli Strike coffee.  Since Basil can't do it every day, if you
want to drink something vague like reverse lipstick coffee, you'll
have to throw it away like walking around with a UGG.
I think it's the same gear product as 5 cuts and things like that. If you do that, it's not so good, but you eat it,
and when you eat something bad for your body, you should drink it for the taste. It
's such a waste. You're a waste, and tactics and 3 always think about
that. Think about the liver and sex ratio. Cheongseong Big Complete Be. Say it. Anyway, Kanye needs to detoxify his liver, so he should drink alcohol that won't be a waste of money. If you're going to drink, it's the same with coffee.
When you drink it, you should always drink something that's too fragrant, too delicious, too ecstatic. It does
n't seem good to pour it in just to get caffeine when you can eat or not eat something that doesn't taste that good.
Mold condenses when coffee beans are roasted. The
mold toxin is released. The roasting under is very high, and
the fruity aroma and sour taste go away.
Give it to me. The CEO of Coffee Kona said that raw. You know a lot about marketing, right?
5.
I don't know much about sincerity. Yes, I'll say
that in the first installment.  I think that Koreans
think Starbucks coffee is delicious, but they say they don't like their own coffee, and
think that hot coffee is delicious. Maybe
it's because they didn't have a last chance to try delicious coffee.
Not everyone is like that, but I
think that's usually the case. If we really talk about [ __ ] coffee, the only thing we've had so far is the
typical single-origin coffee from McDonald's McCafe or the
coffee sold at Sweeperia,
which is some terrible 3-pack coffee that makes you feel like you're drinking
that. Because we drink that, we think that Aco Pay is strange and that we drink something that's hot. And
since Starbucks also sells hot coffee, we think of hot coffee as the standard.
In fact, Korea drinks a lot of coffee, but it's not a country with a long coffee history.
Rather than disliking coffee that makes you sleepy, wouldn't it be more correct to not have tried the 3-pack coffee? That's
just how I think. Is it
good to eat activated charcoal when you're sick or have enteritis?
Ah, you can see. I think it would be good to eat sugar-coated coffee and fast for a bit.
Sighing, you can use activated charcoal or clay.
Ah, really.  I also used to
drink coffee at the end of a matte day. When did you get a coffee? I used to drink coffee, and I
used to change it to coffee after I had a set of 4 coffees, or maybe I had a coffee coupon, and I
drank some coffee, and wow, I
really
ate it. Why do people hate sinker coffee? It's this big. Dark
inside. So, dark roasting, strong distribution, that's not bad.
If you're going to
eat contaminated beans anyway,
strong distribution is better than this.
Phytic acid also disappears a lot when roasted like this.
Mold and toxins are destroyed by heat, so it's safer to roast for a long time at a high temperature. As
for specialty coffee, as I mentioned earlier,
I don't know much about coffee.
5.
Talking about bread, but among the companies I used in the past, it
wasn't LED PL. I wish I had heard of a special. The coffee was so black and
had a strange taste from the coffee. I used to
buy coffee like this at a place like this.
G In the past, this was sent from my roasting that day.
Looking at it like this, the reason I bought it here is because it's just a store. 1. This place is really
cheap.  I had 4 of them,
but the cheap ones aren't just the occasional 10,000 won pairs, and
Sparta
coffees are like this, 200 grams, almost 150 grams. They only
do this much when it's raining.
Oh, if you buy one of these, which is almost 100 grams, you're really eating a lot. If you
want to make coffee once, 20 grams is enough.
If you really
use 5 of those teas, it might not be that bad, but if you
come to 20 at night, you can drink 10 cups of this 10 times, and
then each cup costs 1,500 won. Even if you buy the most expensive one,
this is the Ethiopian Lee. I've
tried everything here, but I
bought an XL specialty coffee and it's about 5,000 won.
I
don't think it's right to
drink coffee by pouring it over the beans unless you pay for the space. It's not difficult to make coffee at home, and the
roasting is even better.
Depending on how you do it, if you
use the current strong wiring,
Rather than saying that Chairman Kang is bad, if you do it with Kang Tae-seon, a lot of the character disappears.
Like this, Bin and Tae-jin, the
expensive ones like Khan Coffee Jin Cheop are really expensive, but this one costs
300,000 won each,
but when I went to sleep, a 1kg hammer was 3 million won, and there are some ridiculously cheap ones. Based on that, you can mix the bark of the manta ray in water and do it. Ah, these days, it's gotten better, so I think I'll use it, but I somehow raised my 4th section last year and had
coffee at Starbucks. I went to
see a friend and
had a drink for the first time in a long time. It was a
5-course meal and I
drank it once and didn't drink any more. It didn't
seem like much, so it's a bit different than before. I think it's changed a lot these days, but
it used to be worse.
Smoke, that's really funny.
Starbucks isn't just part-timers; they're all regulars.
And the original, well, I
think it could vary depending on the condition rather than how the person selects it.
Wonder is delicious,
but strictly speaking, selecting spas
doesn't require skill, so I'll use it
first.  It's the same,
I don't have a shell, that is, my favorite, I don't drink coffee that addictively, so I
drink it for the taste, and I have all kinds of food except cigarettes, but I
don't go as far as to choose paper products by type.  I used to drink a lot of wine and soju, and a
lot of coffee because I didn't have much of a gay streak,
so I just liked the taste of it.
In the past, I
wondered why I didn't do anything special. I should have listened to that story earlier. Even
if I don't necessarily go towards coffee, if I have to go to
war right now, or if I need to know about yogurt and Sauron,
or if I already know that I need to stimulate the sympathetic nervous system, then it would
be helpful to drink it beforehand. Since it's
necessary anyway,
I don't have a plan. There aren't many situations where I
need to show my sympathetic nervous system to anyone.
So, when the truth
comes to 9, I have to drink it right away. So, since it's cheap, I drink it after going out. It's
just
raising the right coat more, so I have
to hurry and decide at that time. The
coffee is consumed quickly. Rather than
pushing the top one in as a prelude, I just put it in as a prelude. Even though it didn't work out earlier,
we just passed it on whether it worked or not.
Since it wasn't that difficult, I just didn't drink coffee like that.
I used it
as a real gear food.  I ate. I was just talking a little
while ago and stopped, but the more I
walk, the more I think about it. It's a really sad story to eat like that because it's a war zone at work. When you go out to fight, when something like that is needed, it
's for those times in
the first place. Chocolate used to be criticized and the seeds would burn. We're just eating time now,
right? Chocolate is a seed,
so there was a time when you ate the seeds. In South America, when those tribes and
natives performed psychedelic rituals,
what's the big deal about the seeds? If you do it with a specific purpose like that, what's the point? It's because you do it
with a clear sense of purpose to do that.
But next time, because you're eating certain things every day to perform psychedelic rituals,
this becomes a problem.
Coffee is also famous. During the American Revolutionary Army's Ringer,
during the Civil War, people said, "If I drink this, I can fight one more day."
In the US, there was something like that. If you
drink caffeine and exercise, you burn body fat better and have more stamina.  It gets better. This is because the
sympathetic nervous system is activated, so the body is in good condition to fight. Sunny
fought. Exercising is about understanding Kim and doing the box.
When Ellen and her son, Ali, come out, the liver's glycogen is
converted into blood sugar by the clicker, and it
does a lot of things like converting protein into glucose. In the process, more fat is produced, so the metabolic rate itself
increases.
Think of our body as a tiger in front of us. In that state, we have to
draw on all the energy we have. We have to
run away right now, so we burn body fat. But it's not just body fat that's burning, it's muscle, so you can lose more body fat. It's possible to lose the same amount of fat as you did
when you called it. Now, by exercising, you
can achieve the effect of losing more body fat.
After the opening, the adrenaline goes up, and the effect is there.
Now, there are side effects.
Because caffeine is so strong, it's
difficult to quit, like alcohol or drugs. The
withdrawal symptoms are the same.  As I
mentioned, I don't drink coffee.
First of all, I feel extremely tired and the
dopamine receptors in my body have decreased. Since I
don't drink coffee, I only release a little dopamine, and I feel tired and a little down.
Labeling, the sound of cocaine, and things like that don't come out as much as they used to, so I feel
less tired and more tired. And so,
cocaine, methamphetamine, and things like that affect the lungs.
Dopamine and adrenaline return to the brain, and I release a huge amount of these things.
Then, I don't feel like I have any. Just keep reading.
Coffee works in that way, so I
don't hit the paradox or strongly suppress it, but it
's difficult in that way. Since I hit it together, the
hypothalamus and the adrenocorticotropic hormone and catecholamines in my ass are
greatly reduced. If you drink a lot of coffee, you
will feel tired. Stop it and screw up.
Ver.
04 Academy. Why did you
feel that headache at the end as pure pain?
Or maybe it was because of the coffee or something? I
think it was because you knew it. Ugh.
[Music]
This is because coffee stimulates the sympathetic nerves, so it's easy to see.  Because they don't come out, the
deep-seated calming substances in the brain don't come out well.
And then, the headache gets worse.
3. Among the things I explained earlier, there are many bad things about coffee.
Ah, especially for children, like Olivia, pregnant women, and those who need it. And
children and teenagers.
Actually, until I was young,
of course, I drank it, but most of my friends drank it, and I
drank it.
Teenagers, there was a perception that coffee was bad for children and that they shouldn't drink it because it was bad for them.
But these days,
drinking coffee is considered very sophisticated and intellectual, and
kids have to drink it to study. At the time, that perception was there, so if
you drink it when you're young, you don't recover well. Well, if you drink it like this when you're a teenager, it's an
anxiety layer,
so it's easy for the sanity-related layer 2 to
end up not returning.
In the g experiment, they
added IMC and reduced coffee.
Caffeine doesn't just penetrate the testis and ovaries, but
there are barriers in the reproductive organs, so not anything can enter.
And now, the placenta and the languor.  There's a barrier. It's
like a 14-sheet wall that blocks anything from entering. There are things that protect the body from blood flow, like a 14-sheet wall.
Coffee
penetrates the placenta even further, and as
soon as you drink it, it spreads throughout the body.
Lemon. So the more you
drink coffee, the more you feel like that during the day. It's good to
drink something before studying or exercising.
Salt. Small building. Big building. Exercise. Add evil incarnation. Stop
it. Drink it like this. About 3g. 30 minutes before you exercise. Then, you'll know much better. MCT oil isn't that great. You can also drink it after sleeping.
Now, I think it's okay to drink it with salt mixed in the first two glasses.
After exercising, what's wrong with your head?
It's good to drink salt before exercising. That way, it's
better for you to move more. I think your exercise ability itself will increase a lot. It's
not bad to wear extra dots. Why can't I?
But first, you need to get better at reading.
Love, integrity, hello,
bulletproof coffee on the market is coffee, more coffee, but
I'm 3.5 years old, and
it's better not to drink something big like pine nuts. It's
okay to do it in a state where you have to listen to it. It's
okay to do it in a big way. Now, in the spring, it's a little more stressful, and environmental stress, so if you can't do it after a while, it's helpful to have some salt before sweating and exercise. Ugh, it's awkward. You don't have to do it right away. The
body has been checked a few times.
Ah,uh, uh,
5.
Hair
loss, 100 times. It's not a hospitalization that I chose.
Now, I've chosen to wear it similarly. I eat l and live up to 3 times.
You all wake up in the morning and go to work out at 5 o'clock.
And before working out,
you eat a building.
What is it? Dwayne Johnson and I are going to do the mountain together. There's a TNT program or something.
MBC Titan Games
4. Ah, you go to work out at 5 o'clock and drink water on a small plate.
When you have a fever, there's a Russian solution.
How do you do it in the bear country?
Seri 8 won. There's a good explanation in this,
so please provide the data.  There's nothing to show you. In Russia, it
seems like it's not good to catch a cold or make contact. So, to
put it simply, they have extreme home sex. They
really go all the way to the end, suck out all the Eau de Casale # salty,
put a raw garlic clove in it, and then go into the sauna. Make it as
hot as you can stand the Milky Way, and stay there for an hour or
two, until you're about to pass out.
This is warm. You endure the sauna until it's almost cold, and
if you feel better, you come out and jump into the ice clothes outside.
After that, they sprout right away.
That's their tradition.
Miss, one by one. Of course,
since your body can withstand 6L at home, it's good for your health, so you can see that.
In other words,
my body
naturally deals with environmental stress and things like notes and alcohol, right?
Reading, reading. Then, eat garlic and
push the story of Cha Eun-taek into the park. Then, when you come, you push your own detoxification ability
to the limit.
Wake her up.  If you
want to follow along similarly, would
n't it be better to go to the sauna, do some weight training, and exercise vigorously while also doing some regular yoga?
Uh,
while taking off the kit, the selection is cold and the shutter is 9, so
try them one by one. 5 If you're going to eat, and I told you that it's better to eat a lot, right?
In the song, the items are
outside, in
Norway, what's
the name? It's like a
part blowing in from the North Sea, and you
wrap the baby in a sling and fill it like this.
That's a piece, but
it's big. It's about raising a charming woman who will become poor. It's a
bit awkward to go to the babies in the flood.
It's not like it's just making it hot. It's a way to squeeze out the sweat, and it's
more expensive. It means that the body sweats a lot, but that doesn't mean that mother,
now that the
10th floor protein heat shock platinum
will be activated, so
take a shower and figure out the stick and neck of mom. You'll be doing it a little bit,
so your usual physical strength and height will be high. Now, it's not like you're going to collapse from a cold, right?
[Music]
Vitamin  A and drink a lot of tea.
What else is there to eat when you stand upright?
Kate also says that viruses and sun atomize.
Oh, there are things that come to mind when you don't talk about them,
but I
think it's important to know if you actually feel pain. If
it's warm when you look at the atoms,
that's because your body temperature rises. That could be why it's
like that. The amount of fat varies depending on the condition of your gums. If you just say it's for dieting purposes, I'll tell you. I don't know anything about the original, but if you eat carbohydrates, it's better to eat enough when you're not in ketosis and metabolizing carbon. It
's vaguely gray before that. It's harder on the body, so it's
cold when you sleep.
Should I do new hair care next time?
Of course, my father won't like it, but I want to raise this tea all night.
In reality, when teenagers do that, people can't sleep and come outside. If it
gets worse, they just can't sleep. It's
not to the point where they're really cold and shivering when they sleep, but you have to make it as cold as possible. Good
night. I didn't do that much.  The electricity bill seems to be high,
but it's not that bad.
Instead, at least wear light clothes and
don't cover them with thick leaves.
Yes, but that's the tradition for newborns sleeping outdoors. What's the
big deal? It's
cold and then hot, then cold and hot. It's probably because of this. Maybe it's
just
because Beckham Tikki slept.
When you sighed,
[music]
it's good, but
yeah, this
fever is still high, but wouldn't the remaining days be a little better? After that job is over, I've
given a lot so far. Powell Tomato's leptin is really full. It's a
lot, but still,
cherry tomatoes. You really have no reason to eat them now. They're
not that tasty.
Of course, there are many people who do bottom aster, but there are many who drink tomatoes
first. For example, if you compare them to similar sizes, plums are tastier, right? There are more tangerines, and it feels a little different, but I'd rather eat plain ones. Cherry tomatoes are not good for your body. The uh, sleeping without a knife seems difficult at first, but
I sleep too much.  It's hot,
but the house is low, so
there were too many lights, and it was too noisy outside,
so I couldn't sleep for 10 minutes. This part should all be turned off, but it was
too hot to plug all the doors in, so
there are some people who don't like
fuel. It really feels like they just threw away sugar, but when I compared the sizes with my wife, it's true. You can
also eat cherry tomatoes that don't like Singer. It
means peach.
Okay, I don't know about the academy, but it kills mosquitoes, so it's
not good for us.
It's hard to peel the small skin, so if you peel it like this when it's ripe, you can
peel it like this, but if you're trying to eat one of those tiny things, it
's a bit like that. It's
a pity, but if you go and put on shoes and look at it, the
egg law is exactly like that.
It's good if the sea water lapping at your neck like this, but
summer-born people need to get a lot of sunlight to tear and grow big. When they're young, they eat
cod liver oil and things like that.  I don't have vitamin tea, and I eat vitamin A. They
don't get diabetes when they grow up. In fact, when a mother is pregnant, the
child's fate is determined by how the mother gives birth.
Yes, so it's said that all of the Canadian aborigines' children are
born in the same month. How about meeting them all in June? That's because of the weather, but
in August, when
summer came, they hunted and ate a lot of Carrie Bora moose. Carrie Brown
moose are full, and when summer came, they all came down to the ground to mate.
At that time, the thyroid glands of the moose that came down during the mating season were said to be
extremely enlarged. They catch these moose, eat the thyroid gland, and
then have children.
That's why they were all born in June. They
all came out in the same month and around the same time. There may
be some differences depending on the region. It
can't be good for them to be born on the same day because they're tied to the equator.
In our country, it
would be better to give birth in June and give birth in the summer.
Here, there are copies,
so I think it's too expensive
to buy just one. It's better to buy a lot.  It's cheap, right?
Even if it's summer color, summer raw,
eat a lot of that
and then you can
eat cod liver and get rid of the burp. Does the burp get better? It's like
eating a lot of liver and eating food, so
try eating it with food.
Of course, we'll
see what the situation is like then, but when you
have resistance resources,
dig up the child and do an ultrasound, and it's
better not to do physical education because it's in
the garage. In the world, it's like that. Teak. I told you how bad the ultrasound test is. App testing is ridiculous. If you're going to do egg testing, let's do it together. Do 12 at a time. The burp was bad every time you ate the range section.
Ah, ah, I
don't know what could cause Daegok yoga training. There
could be allergies in Daegu. Yes, g
cream pattern tests all heavy metals. Buy something that
tests. It was a
heat pump 5 and
ah, and Jeon Geum-seok. As I mentioned, it's
already over from the fact that the Eskimos didn't get heavy metal poisoning. In fact,
if the Creole must was more severe, just take Omega 3 itself.  I think you might accept the law.
Omega 3 is
4. Even so, the reason for the coronation is that you
have to eat it. Half a teaspoon, maybe 1 teaspoon. It's not a lot, but if
your mom
doesn't like it with food, it
might be better not to eat it.
But it's so good to know.
What kind of school judge do you eat it with?
Thailand. No. If you eat it with cream pass, is that okay?
Eskimos used a lot of tobacco. People who inhaled a lot of smoke. Now,
African tribes smoke a lot. In the Kara Hell Breath Islands,
in Tablet S,
ah, yesterday,
I burst, and I put cream on it again. Is
it better to prepare the Tablet S story separately?
To give you a rough explanation, let's talk about it next time. The Roman of the press
probably wrote it himself or something. It
was called Black Cows in Tablet S Jed. It's
the same as us. It's like a thatched house with light b, and there's land like this and it reaches here. The
Tablet S Islands' staple food was cod, North Korea, cod, fish, and
oats. Oh,
oats here.  The land was so poor that these people couldn't grow trees. There
weren't any trees, and since there weren't many, they could
n't grow anything else, so they couldn't raise animals. For animals to thrive, like cattle, they
had to graze on grass. But grass didn't do well, so the
ground was the first floor of the tortilla. Now, here, in this completely shabby, movie-
free land, we had to plant ears and let them grow. To do that, we
had to provide them with special needs. And there was just one thing that worked: to
heat the peat in this chip, like this, over the stove.
So, they dug up the peat and brought it here. They burned the grass and
piled up straw, like oats,
on top, and the
smoke just rose. It was made according to refraction. In our country, ondol is like
this. You light an iPhone here, and it passes through like this on location, and now it's here. Now, this is the
point.
4. There's no chimney here, no cold girl. Yes,
but they left the grass. If you just light a brazier, the smoke will rise like this
inside the house.  I'll teach you, it's full in the house, but for that, it's just straw, so 2 It
goes around and around like this, like this, it's not going to extend to one room,
right?
If you escape like this, if you burn Lee Young-gi's peat, chicory smoke comes out.
Do you know what Toto is? To you, that C-cut smoke
changes in front of the computer you've learned like this, so you're startled. 2
How about solving this in a Black House way? And now, the picture is going
to be strict.
When the farming is processed, they say they tore off the entire thatched roof above the smoke and used it as fertilizer for the ground.
That's the only way to profit. They say my ears caught it well, but
these people burned peat at home and just continued to live there.
But one more person didn't get tuberculosis, and at the time, tuberculosis was a real problem for other people.
In the beginning, for 1,500 won,
let alone solving it, they didn't get any other diseases.
And other people, Western civilization is trapped and falling from the outside.
If you eat Taewoong smoke at home like this, it's not good, so I
came out here and filmed the house separately and
didn't light it here.  They said they smoked and made a sequel.
And now civilization ate food. Then, everyone got sick and
all the sprouts fell out. Children were ruined and all that.
So, if you
eat healthily, if you
fill up on this kind of Lee Young-gi, a lot of dioxin and other things are released. Some
people smoke, but this is really just
living here. For a moment, they said it was okay despite the work here, so if you
add something similar to this, you have to
choose broadcast content next. In Africa, they
build sharp huts like this and say, "
How about a pro?
And now, at the end of the ou, you
can go out here. It's not enough, so I have to go out here." So, if you
smoke like this, the inside will be filled with smoke. Because it's
filled with smoke, malaria mosquitoes can't come in from outside. They bounce
off.
There are more of these, so I
lived like this. They say they protected themselves from this. Hey, hey, smoke, and card cards,
and he lived like this, but his health is perfect.
So, that
media outlet said that I put a lot of incense and things like that, and then my stomach is a little different, but
I
don't necessarily think that drinking and smoking is healthy.  I don't think it's impossible.
Nicotine is a bit different, but I heard that skimmers smoked a lot.
There weren't any motels, and
those carcinogens
just burn the balls. There are more.
In that case, smoke is just completely together. Tar and
such will be in the peat.
People who usually do ec casting
eat 5 pieces of paper a day, right?
If you do it a day, you have to eat 30 pieces. So, it's ridiculous. Shinji, I'll just pass on the
IOPE casting. Why not attach the text in front of it?
When there is no addition of 400 million or more, 28 colors, the album egg is a dead gray. When there is no brothel, the
yolk color is closer to the light, so is
it better than salmon yolk? Yes, if you
graze a lot outside,
eat a lot of green iron, and eat a lot of notebooks, the yolk color will be orange.
Even if you eat it with a creamy texture, if it is
like that, it is a boast. If it comes out, you should fill it with something else, such as 00. It seems that
Omega 3 and such don't suit you well. It hurts.  The
things that came out of the refinement
weren't specifically recommended like that, but you need to know that big thing. I told you this before, right?
If you look at the studies that people who say that song is bad for you bring up, the relative risk of the Wella item is 1.15, 1.13, and
0.9. I told you that it's a completely meaningless
level, and if it doesn't go over 2, it's
meaningless, but that m51 point is like this, and so they're
talking about something that's really useless, and they used cigarettes as an example.
Then, I showed you that the relative risk is not even e, but in some
cases, it's over 100. In the video,
it's definitely not good. You can absolutely deny that. It's not good. The
relative test score of 100 means that there are almost 3 problems.
Of course, it's not 100 in all cases, but usually it's a little over cp.
But now, you can't say for sure that smoking can't lead to a healthy life. The
relative salt content is 102, which is too much of a margin. The
relative risk is over 100.  It was the wind, it was like
this.
Number 1 above is certain. It's
better to cut off number 3. I'm absolutely not telling you that it's good for P.
Oh, those people were healthy and
died, so everyone is P. This isn't it. Key and Sang-sang can live healthily today, but does the other party exceed Constitution 101 or 102?
So, I have to take out the presentation I made before and show you the form. It
doesn't make sense for a taxi to exceed this.
Fabian Danas
talked about terrorism.
If the meat of the dog is bad, then the genealogy is nonsense. I threw this away, so it
's not a PPT. If you watch
my video, Ah, Ji-young, then for
a moment, here is the data. It
's here.
Oh, you can
see this. Let's
zoom in a little.
This is the song. Late Square
Red Life 6. What is
this? Processing. Here,
how much does the L's Rote Disc have? If it doesn't exceed e, it's not worth researching.
That study is
square 1.28. Colon cancer occurs 1.28.
Schedule 5. 1.00. We have no risk, and
our workplace is visible. Colon. Like this.  If you ride the colon, that's right.
1.18 1.11 1.0 9
1.6 It doesn't go over.
Um, my
daughter, the next is another data
I have below. I used that and stuff,
but if you look at the rooting risk interest for this, it's like 0.72 and 0.93, and
there's a lot of treatment. There are also things that reduce the risk by eating there.
But in fact, these don't have a next. It means that it's meaningless if you don't go over almost gay.
Well, wherever you look, 1.17 1.18
1.35 1.0 6 give reference 4 0 points I hate Lee Young-cheol 7 is these things, but
somewhere 4 4 ​​How about cigarettes?
Ugh, protein like this Rum
Tenska Sun The probability that it can be caught
at that time 1 Taean rag The probability is also 111
108 re 8.5 28.0
28 and 54.1 Let's
forget the lower ones 19.0 44.2 Doctor 69.8
Especially 111 108
This is the next one, is it
really true? You can never say that smoking is absolutely okay.
Backpack 11 days,
meat 0.93 1.3 108 111 cigarettes, right?
You know, app,
tls,
stress, loan, goodness, all, coffee, it's okay, right? Drinking like that
puts the body into a state of strong stress, so
it's like that.
Iz, I have to organize the broadcast.
I think there's no such thing when talking about smoking or smoking.
But today, I
'll finish Samsung like this. I'm
absolutely not talking about smoking, so
quit smoking. You can also do coffee, put it in, and
cook it.
It's good to reduce 7 degrees. Quitting is more sugar,
so the ideal thing is to not do that. It's
not that you have to do it.
Yes,
thank you for watching. Bye. I'll see you on Wednesday.
Arc. We're getting next Saturday. Are we going? We're
going to the playground. We're going to have work
that day. We're a bit busy that day.
Dirt 2.
Thank you for coming.
Many of you have joined our cafe.  Please do it